prolimehost.com 2017-10-23

# Our Privacy Policy | ProlimeHost

####  Prolimehost: Privacy Policy

Our privacy policy describes how Prolimehost managed and use the customer information and visitors of our website. The terms of the privacy policy are interconnected with acceptable usage policy and our terms of services. 

##### Collection of Information

Prolimehost collect the information from the website at different points. We offer services with the help of third party processors and share the collected information to conduct the business activities. 

We save and collect user information from our website. The purpose of our privacy policy is to let our user know what type of information we collect and how we treat it. We reserve the rights to change our policy at any time. 

In order to be a member of our business user may register for our services using the registration form. The demographic information and subscription to our newsletter is personalized and optional while registering. 

For online purchase we required valid information such as name email address and shipping address along with financial information to process and approve the purchase order. This information is solely used for billing and execute the purchase order, in case of any trouble we contact the user at the provided email address. 

We save the information collected via cookies, logs , and third party softwares to create users profile. This information is used to help the customers to visit our website and communication with them. Your profile is never shared to un-authentic third party processors. 

##### Cookies

The cookie is the data saved on the user’s computer while browsing our website. We use session id based cookies which means the cookie simply terminated as the browser is closed. You can also remove persistent cookies from your browser following the specific browser instructions. 

##### Log Files

As a standard our web server collects logs including IP addresses, type of browsers, your local internet provider ISP, your platform, time stamp, and Geo based information to analyse user movement on our server and website. 

##### Our Newsletter

We send a welcome email to all our new users and occasionally we send the promotional offers and company news to our established customers. We allow the user to chose the option not to receive such type of communication during registration process. We also provide a way to unsubscribe our newsletter by opt-out link in our emails. 

##### Service Related Announcements

At certain times we may send necessary service related notices to users. Such as, your service is suspended or we have a sudden maintenance tasks on our servers. Usually we do not offer opt-out option in such communication, however the user still have the optionto cancel the services or deactivate his own account. 

##### Prolimehost Disclaimer

We do our best to preserve the user information and privacy, however we may disclose your personal data information in order to cooperate with law and regulations. we believe that it is a necessary process to keep the law and order and we cooperate with legal authorities. 

##### Prolimehost Business Transitions

If Prolimehost undergoes the business transition, such as selling or merging a part of a company or being acquired by another company, the user information will be the part of asset transferred to another company. We will notify the user with details prior to the transition. 

##### Website Links

Prolimehost is linked to other websites, you must be aware we do not take any responsibility of the privacy policy of other sites linked to us. We highly recommend our users to read the policy before leaving our website.

##### Purchasing History

In order to serve better we may compare the users preferences and purchasing habits with our partner websites to create your personalized profile.

##### Additional Terms of Service

Prolimehost reserve the rights to change or update our terms of services and privacy policy at any time with or without notices to our customers.

Learn More
